<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>hat's nekocomiccon</title>
        <description>#1 Hina Fansite!</description>
        <link>https://hat.neocities.org/</link>
        <lastBuildDate>January 1, 1970 12:00:00 AM</lastBuildDate>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 30, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#127</link>
            <description>A new Halloween photo of Praline is now online! Added the link to the housefire doll thread in the doll memories page. Added a link to someone who knows more about these strange chinese doll recasts in doll opinions (they're not BJD!) Added massive sized dolls to the BJD guide.</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 24, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>blog 126</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#126</link>
            <description>New photos of Verona and Cheby! Typo fix in the doll guide.</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 23, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>minor updates</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#links</link>
            <description>Links page has been rehauled. About page was edited and now includes stamps. Favorites page has been unlinked from the nav bar. I'm very indecisive about this!</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 22, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>WOW! Blog 125 is here already? No way!!</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#125</link>
            <description>Added another neocities BJD owner to the doll links list, added a few more people to the VIP doll links section. I added more doll issues and migrated a few from Doll Memories. In their place is an old memory of an Impldoll boy. A collection of stamps is now available! Link is at the bottom of my about page.</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 18, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>Japanese Kabedon is here!</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#124</link>
            <description>Cheby finally got his own gallery page and a new profile pic. A few other dolls got updated pics as well! I started a list of issues with BJD companies that have occured. There are many more issues to add. Wish me luck!</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 13, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>Blog 123 is here!</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#123</link>
            <description>I hope you didn't notice I missed 2 questions in the 2022 BJD Questionnaire! I definitely did not miss 55 and 77! I went through my doll blog log after discovering a small group of bloggers still left on Blogspot. I got a few more in there and moved around the ones that died in the last few months. RIP. I added a CSS file for this RSS feed. Why didn't anyone tell me RSS was awesome??</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 10, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>Worms have arrived!</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#questionnaires/BJDowner100Q2022</link>
            <description>I filled out the massive 100 question doll questionnaire! New photo added to the furby shrine, WIP page "worms" has been completed and added to shrines. Favorites page has been relinked again. Reviews for 2 APC albums added to music reviews. Added links to all my doll videos and the two questionnaires in doll memories.</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 5, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>Blog #122 has arrived</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#122</link>
            <description>Hina NFT installed as a link to this RSS feed! Isn't she cute? Two Japanese Volks wiki links added to the Volks shrine along with Aridede's design sheet for SD16 Diamond. A furby collection page has been created.</description>
        </item>

        <item>
            <pubDate>October 2, 2022</pubDate>
            <title>Blog #121 has arrived!</title>
            <link>https://hat.neocities.org/home.html#121</link>
            <description>New blog post, new RSS feed! Added a page on FCS SD-F-100 finalists and moved some stuff around for the VolksUSA online FCS ordering information into a new page.</description>
        </item>

    </channel>
</rss>